https://www.azimpact.com/privacy.htm

Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (https://www.azimpact.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you
through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are
the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have
access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or
other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information
to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason
you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third
party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill
your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future
to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this
privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You
may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the
following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone
number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a
site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and
identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a
cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more
than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also
enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the
experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any
personally identifiable information on our site.
Security
We take precautions to protect your
information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your
information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data),
that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.
You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and
looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted
online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who
need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or
customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable
information. The computers/servers in which we store personally
identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately through our contact form.
We are currently available for work. Please, contact us for a quote
